allaboutdance.com 2015-06-23

# All About Dance - Privacy Statement

Privacy Statement

At All About Dance, we treat your privacy with utmost respect. This document should answer any questions you may have regarding user privacy and our web site. 

* **Information Collection and Use**

All About Dance is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, rent or give this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. All About Dance collects information from our users at several different points on our web site.  **Ordering**

We request information from the user during our order process. Here a user must provide contact information (such as name and address) and may provide financial information (such as a credit card number). This information is used for billing purposes and order fulfillment. If we have trouble processing an order, the contact information is used to get in touch with the user. (See also Additional Uses and Choice/Opt-out below.) 

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on a user's hard drive containing information related to your use of the web site. We currently set cookies on your browser in order to track your shopping cart and wish list. We do not store any personal information in these cookies, only a reference number to assist you in the ordering process. If you choose to place an order with us, the cookie will be removed when your order is placed. Otherwise, it will expire 24 hours after your initial visit to our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback is that you may not be able to place more than one item in your shopping cart. 

All About Dance utilizes various services to gather performance information on visitors to our site. This information may be gathered utilizing cookies provided by a third party. These cookies contain NO personally identifiable information and are only used to gather performance statistics.

**Log Files**

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act)**

All About Dance will never knowingly collect personally identifiable information from a person under the age of 13 without verifiable parental consent. If we become aware of a situation where we have collected personally identifiable information from a person under 13 years of age without parental consent we will remove the information from our records. 

* **Information Sharing**

We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and/or advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

We use a credit card processing company to bill users for purchases. This company does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purpose. 

Occasionally we may provide our mailing list to partners that we feel our users would like to receive information from. The information provided will only include your name and mailing address, it will **NOT** include your telephone number, credit card information, e-mail address, ordering information/habits or any other personally identifiable information. If you do not wish to have your information included in this list we provide an opt-out choice for our customers as detailed below. 

These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purposes of providing these services. 

All About Dance has partnered with Affinion Corporation to offer the Great Fun discount service. At the completion of your order you will be offered the chance to sign up for this service in return for receiving a rebate on your purchased. If you click on the offer link you will be taken to the Great Fun sign-up page where you will be able to read the terms and conditions of the offer. If you decide to accept the offer, the credit card you used to make your purchase will be transmitted via secure means to Affinion Corporation for the purposes of purchasing their offer. If you do not accept the offer on the sign-up screen your credit card information WILL NOT be transmitted. The Great Fun service is administered by Affinion and other than offering this service to you All About Dance has no connection with it in any way.

* **Link Issues**

This web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we, All About Dance, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site. 

* **Security**

This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card numbers), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as those that encompass our order process, the lock icon on the bottom of web browsers (such as Netscape Navigator or Microsoft Internet Explorer) becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are "just surfing." 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, customer service representatives and order processing employees) are granted access to personally identifiable information. All employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are kept in a securely locked environment. 

If you have any questions about security at our web site, you can write to info@allaboutdance.com. 

* **Additional Uses & Choice/Opt-out**

Telephone Solicitations Users will never be solicited by telephone for any product offer. They may be contacted by phone if there is a problem or question about an order that they have placed. Also, from time to time, we may phone a small percentage of our customers in order to conduct quality assurance surveys. These surveys are optional and take place only on rare occasions. 

* **Email Solicitations**

From time to time we may offer additional email communications (such as a newsletter, special offers, site update notifications, etc); customers may choose not to be included in these e-mail messages by using the customer service section as well as following the instructions included in the email itself. 

* **Choice/Opt-out**

Customers will always be provided with an opportunity to opt out of any mailings or telephone calls not directly related to order fulfillment. If you are an existing customer and wish to opt out of any mailings please see our customer service section. 

* **Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, notification will be linked from our homepage to the new policy so that our users are always up-to-date on what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances (if any) we disclose it. Users will be notified via email and presented with an opportunity to opt-out should we decide to use information in a manner that is inconsistent with the way in which it was collected 

* **Contact Information**

We are here to help you in any way possible, please feel free to contact us using one of these methods    
**Via E-mail** [info@allaboutdance.com](mailto:info@allaboutdance.com)   
**Via Phone for Ordering** 1-800-775-0578 M-F 6am-5pm PST, Sat 7am-3pm PST   
**Via Phone for General Questions** 1-800-775-0578 M-F 6am-5pm PST, Sat 7am-3pm PST   
**Via Snail Mail** All About Dance   
180 Welles St, Suite 500   
Forty Fort, PA 18704
